[
    {
      "title": "20th Century British History"
    },
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "In which year did Queen Victoria die, marking the end of the Victorian era?",
      "answer": "1901"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Who became the British Prime Minister in 1940, leading the country through WWII?",
      "answer": "Winston Churchill"
    },
 
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which British Prime Minister served from 1979 to 1990?",
      "answer": "Margaret Thatcher"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "The BBC first began regular television broadcasts in which year: 1936 or 1954?",
      "answer": "1936"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which year did King George V ascend to the British throne?",
      "answer": "1910"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which British colonial possession was returned to China in 1997?",
      "answer": "Hong Kong"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which British code-breaking center led by Alan Turing played a crucial role in WWII?",
      "answer": "Bletchley Park"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "In what year did women gain equal voting rights with men in the UK?",
      "answer": "1928"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which conflict from 1919 to 1921 is also referred to as the Anglo-Irish War?",
      "answer": "The Irish War of Independence"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "In which year was the National Health Service (NHS) established?",
      "answer": "1948"
    }
  ]